You@It should be fixed now, right?
僕@たぶん直ったかな
You@Alright, we've got water now.
僕@水出たよ
Shirley@Not bad at all.
シャーリイ@スゴイです
Shirley@A rich heir actually fixing the bathroom with his own hands.
シャーリイ@自分で直せるなんてさすがですね
You@I'm sorry about that.
僕@ごめん
You@For making you all put up with this broken bathroom for so long.
僕@直すまで時間かかって
Shirley@At least you have a conscience.
シャーリイ@直してくれて良かったです、じゃないと…
You@Otherwise what?
僕@じゃないと何？
Shirley@Otherwise, I might have started looking for a new place to live.
シャーリイ@じゃないと新居探すところでした
You@The company's a bit tight on money lately.
僕@会社がピンチなんだ
You@When things get better,
僕@ちょっと待ってくれ
You@I'll definitely buy you all a dryer to make up for it.
僕@良くなったら乾燥機買うから
Shirley@Alright, alright.
シャーリイ@分かりました
Shirley@I know you've been working hard lately.
シャーリイ@最近忙しそうですもんね
Shirley@Here,
シャーリイ@汗、拭いてあげますよ
You@Thank you.
僕@ありがとう
Shirley@Since you fixed the bathroom for us,
シャーリイ@良かったら
Shirley@I'll make you a cup of coffee.
シャーリイ@直してくれたお礼に、コーヒー淹れますよ
You@Sure, that'd be great.
僕@いいね
You@I'll go change my clothes.
僕@着替えてくるので待っててください
You@Give me a moment.
僕@分かった
Shirley@Okay.
シャーリイ@砂糖なしのコーヒーです
Shirley@Your coffee, no sugar.
シャーリイ@ありがとう
You@Thank you.
僕@どうしたんですか？
Shirley@What's wrong?
シャーリイ@仕事の事考えてます？
Shirley@Are you still thinking about work?
シャーリイ@うん
You@Yeah,
僕@最近、バーのスタッフが全員辞めたんだ
You@All the waiters at the bar have quit recently.
僕@スタッフ探せなかったら閉めないとかも
You@If we can't find new staff soon, we might have to close down.
僕@大変ですね
Shirley@That sounds tough.
シャーリイ@そんな事になってるなんて知らなかったです
Shirley@I had no idea you were going through so much lately.
シャーリイ@もし知ってれば
Shirley@If I'd known, I wouldn't have caused trouble with renting out your room.
シャーリイ@部屋が貸せなくなることしないのに
You@Oh, you dare bring that up?
僕@言い過ぎだよ
You@Even people coming to view the room have decreased recently.
僕@最近内見する人も少ないし
You@It feels like it's getting harder to rent it out.
僕@貸し出すのは難しいかもな
Shirley@I'm sorry about that.
シャーリイ@ごめんなさい
Shirley@How about I try to find some other people to come?
シャーリイ@他に借りたい人探してみましょうか
You@Of course, that'd be great.
僕@ありがたいよ
You@The more, the better.
僕@たくさん声かけてみてくれ
You@Speaking of which,
僕@そういえば、レジーナと話した？
You@Have you chatted with Regina recently?
僕@なんか変なんだよね
You@She's been acting a bit strange.
僕@どこがですか？
Shirley@Strange how?
シャーリイ@最近暑いからかな
You@It's been a bit hot lately, right?
僕@何かあったと思って来てみたんだ
You@So I came to check if there were any problems in the dorm.
僕@入口で見かけたんだけど
You@But I saw her downstairs wearing a large coat and acting all sneaky.
僕@なんか大きな服着て、こそこそしてしてたんだ
You@Like she was afraid of me seeing her.
僕@見られたくないみたい
Shirley@Oh, yeah.
シャーリイ@確かに
Shirley@I've seen her going out at night wearing a big coat recently.
シャーリイ@最近出かける時大きめの服着てるかも
Shirley@Maybe she's got a boyfriend?
シャーリイ@彼氏でもできたのかも
You@That's possible.
僕@そうかもね
You@She seems like the type who'd completely change when she gets a boyfriend.
僕@彼氏できたら性格変わるタイプだよね
Shirley@Alright, let's not worry about her.
シャーリイ@なんでもいいですよ
Shirley@I'm going to livestream tonight to sell some clothes I designed.
シャーリイ@今日の夜ライブ配信で服売るんですよ
Shirley@Want to help me out?
シャーリイ@協力してくれますか？
Shirley@I could use an assistant.
シャーリイ@助手が欲しいんですよ